1812 Freemason Bible found in a dumpster
in Aiken, South Carolina is uploaded.
We've also uploaded a number of other
books. The physics [music] and
physiology of spiritualism from 1871,
what a banger. The history of the Jews,
that's kind of fun. Flavius Joseph and
my personal favorite, ancient magic,
magnetism, and psychic forces. As stated
before, viewing the Bible we free for
all. If you would like to download one
of these other books, it will be on a
donation basis only. If you would like
to download or screenshot the Bible for
your personal use, you will have to
[music] be in the subscriber channel.
That will cost 7 or 13 measly dollars a
month to be able to access image search,
AI search, [music] and download sections
to add into the discussion board where
you can discuss this in a public forum
with no censorship. I do not want to
charge any money for this at all, but I
have to because I have to make a
database that is self-supporting.
[music] So, if anything happens to me or
I get put in a box by the FBI, the
database will continue. It must be
self-supporting declining outside
contributions so it can live forever.
[music] And I am really tired of tire
kickers just begging for stuff for free.
I'm busting my ass through this and
spending tens of thousands of dollars
and months of my life. Jesus said if you
seek, you will find. He didn't say if
you ask, if you beg. Seek has a certain
implication of effort on your part.
[music] The plan is to open this up for
about 100 users to go in there and test
everything. So, if we have any kinks, we
can see them and fix them before we open
it up to the entire world. Those who are
selected will get a pre-registration
email saying they got access. Shout out
to Juan Compas. Hello from Buenos Aires.
I'm Juan Compas and I hope you enjoy to
bring back to life this really old book.
>> And shout out to Alex Hoskins who has
scanned and uploaded more pages than
anyone else. In closing, I'd like to
remind you, what would Jesus do is more
than a bracelet.